CAMPUS ALERT  

The Marquette University campus is closed Thursday, Feb. 16, 2023, due to severe weather conditions in the greater Milwaukee area. All classes are canceled regardless of modality – in-person, synchronous and asynchronous online. [More information on Marquette Today.](https://today.marquette.edu/2023/02/marquette-university-campus-closed-feb-16-2023-due-to-severe-weather/) 

* [marquette.edu](https://www.marquette.edu/) //
* [Search](https://www.marquette.edu/search/) //
* [A-Z Index](https://www.marquette.edu/tools/atoz.php) //

[Marquette.edu](https://www.marquette.edu/) // [Tools](https://www.marquette.edu/tools/) // 

Privacy Policy
==============

Marquette University is committed to respecting your privacy. Our privacy policy is clear: We collect no information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us, other than information automatically collected and stored as described below.

Information Automatically Collected
-----------------------------------

When you browse through any website, certain information about you can be collected. We automatically collect and temporarily store the following information about your visit to a Marquette University web site:

* the date and time of your visit;
* the pages you visited; and
* the address of the website from which you came.

We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful and accessible to visitors. Unless you choose to submit it, no additional information is collected about you.

Portions of the Marquette website use Google Analytics, a web metrics service of Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies, which are commonly used text files stored in your browser, to help analyze how users use the site. This cookie information (including your IP address and the Marquette web pages you visit) will be collected by Google and stored on Google servers. Google will use this information to help Marquette understand and evaluate your use of the website. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or when third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

Portions of the website use Microsoft Clarity, which also uses cookies and other tracking technologies to capture data that helps us make informed decisions on the design and function of the website.

To help improve and enhance our users’ experience, we use software tools that detect problems with the website, including broken links, accessibility and quality issues, including Siteimprove and Omni CMS. We also use tools that use search query data and search link clicks to manage and optimize search results for uses, including Omni CMS.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do disable cookies, you may not be able to use the full functionality of portions of the Marquette website (e.g. the MU Connect online alumni community). By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

Portions of the website use Resonate audience insights tags. Learn more about [Resonate privacy principles](https://www.resonate.com/privacy-principles/) or [opt out](http://www.resonate.com/privacy-policy/opt-out-success/).

Personally Provided Information
-------------------------------

Marquette University does not require you provide personal information to visit our website; however, you may choose to provide us with personal information through an e-mail message, form, survey, chat or application. This information is used only to fulfill the stated purpose of your communication or participation. If you are applying to become a student, you can [learn more about how and when your personally provided information may be collected and used here](https://www.marquette.edu/tools/privacy-personal-info-use.php).

Other Marquette Websites
------------------------

Marquette offers other websites that are hosted externally from Marquette. These include:

###   
Marquette Spirit Shop Purchases

Marquette Spirit Shop is hosted externally from Marquette. Personal information submitted to complete online purchases through "The Marquette Spirit Shop" is used only to ship and process your order, and is not shared, sold, bartered or leased to third-party vendors.

###   
GoMarquette.com

GoMarquette.com, the official website of Marquette Athletics, is hosted externally from Marquette. A separate privacy policy currently governs end-user visits and participation.

###   
EagleExpress

EagleExpress, the student shuttle service, is a mobile application from Marquette that is powered by Via. A separate [privacy policy](https://www.marquette.edu/university-safety/transportation/eagle-express/privacy-policy.php) currently governs EagleExpress usage.  

How Your Personal Information is Used
-------------------------------------

Marquette University does not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our online visitors to third parties except as required by law. We use your information to improve your experience on our website and to provide you with the educational or other services you may request from us.

Endorsement Disclaimer
----------------------

Our website has links to many other non-profit, educational, and governmental institutions, and in a few cases, private organizations. You are subject to that site's Privacy Policy when you leave this site. Reference in this website to any specific service, company, or organization does not constitute its endorsement or recommendation by Marquette University. Marquette University is not responsible for the contents of any "off-site" Web page that you may access from this server.

General Info
------------

Phone
-----

(800) 222-6544 or  
(414) 288-7250 for local calls

General address
---------------

Marquette University  
1250 W. Wisconsin Avenue  
Milwaukee, WI 53233

Mailing address
---------------

Marquette University  
P.O. Box 1881  
Milwaukee, WI 53201-1881

* * *

PROBLEM WITH THIS WEBPAGE?
--------------------------

To report another problem, please contact [webrequests@marquette.edu](mailto:webrequests@marquette.edu).

Location

**Marquette University**  
Milwaukee, WI 53233  
**Phone:** (800) 222-6544

Key Resources

MARQUETTE A to Z

© 2024 Marquette University
